<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2016 Jiri Eischmann <eischmann@redhat.com> -->
<component type="desktop">
	<id>org.fedoraproject.MediaWriter.desktop</id>
	<launchable type="desktop-id">org.fedoraproject.MediaWriter.desktop</launchable>
	<project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
	<metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
	<name>Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="ar">كاتب وسائط فيدورا</name>
	<name xml:lang="az">Fedora Media Yazıcı</name>
	<name xml:lang="be">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="bg">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="ca">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="cs">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="da">Fedora-medieskriver</name>
	<name xml:lang="de">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="es">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="eu">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="fi">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="fil">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="fr">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="fur">Scritôr Supuarts di Fedora</name>
	<name xml:lang="he">כותב המדיה של Fedora</name>
	<name xml:lang="hr">Fedora zapisnik medija</name>
	<name xml:lang="hu">Fedora médiaíró</name>
	<name xml:lang="id">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="it">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="ka">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="kn">ಫೆಡೋರ ಮಾಧ್ಯಮ</name>
	<name xml:lang="ko">페도라 미디어 작성기</name>
	<name xml:lang="ml">ഫെഡോറ മാധ്യമ എഴുതുപകരണം </name>
	<name xml:lang="nl">Fedora mediaschrijver</name>
	<name xml:lang="pa">ਫੇਡੋਰਾ ਮੀਡੀਆ ਰਾਇਟਰ</name>
	<name xml:lang="pl">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="pt">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="pt-br">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="ru">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="sk">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="sl">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="sq">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="sr">Fedora Писач Медија</name>
	<name xml:lang="sv">Fedora Mediaskrivare</name>
	<name xml:lang="ta">ஃபெடோரா ஊடக எழுதி </name>
	<name xml:lang="tr">Fedora Ortam Yazıcı</name>
	<name xml:lang="uk">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="zh-cn">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="zh-tw">Fedora 媒體寫入器</name>
	<summary>A tool to create a live USB drive with an edition of Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="ar">أداة لإنشاء محرك أقراص USB يقوم بتشغيل إحدى إصدارات فيدورا مباشرةً</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="az">Fedora Buraxılışı ilə Live USB diski yaratmaq üçün bir vasitədir</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="be">Інструмент для стварэння Live USB-дыска з Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="bg">Инструмент за създаване на USB устройство с живо издание на Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="ca">Una eina per a la creació d'una unitat USB autònoma amb una edició de Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="cs">Nástroj pro vytváření živých USB disků s některou z edicí Fedory</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="da">Et værktøj til at oprette et live-USB-drev med en udgave af Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="de">Ein Werkzeug, um einen Live-USB-Datenträger mit einer Ausgabe von Fedora zu erzeugen</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="es">Una herramienta para crear USB vivos con una edición de Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="fa">یک ابزار برای ایجاد یک USB لایو با یک نسخهٔ فدورا</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="fi">Luo USB-muistitikku, jolta voi käynnistää jonkin Fedoran version</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="fil">Isang tool para gumawa ng live USB drive na may edisyon ng Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="fr">Un outil pour créer un disque USB live avec une édition de Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="fur">Un strument par creâ une unitât USB Live cuntune edizion di Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="he">כלי ליצירת כונן USB חי עם מהדורה של Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="hr">Alat stvaranja pokretljivog USB uređaja za izdanja Fedore</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="hu">Egy eszköz indítható live USB meghajtó készítéséhez a Fedora egy változatával</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="id">Alat untuk menciptakan drive USB live dengan suatu edisi Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="it">Uno strumento per creare unità USB live con una edizione di Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="ja">Fedoraの特定のエディションのLive USBドライブを作成できるツールです</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="ka">ხელსაწყო Fedora-ის ცოცხალი USB დისკის შესაქმნელად</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="ko">페도라 배포판을 실시간 USB 드라이브를 생성하는 도구</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="ml">ലൈവ് ആയ ഇമേജ് ഡിസ്കിനെ USB ഡ്രൈവ് ആകുന്ന ഉപകരണം </summary>
	<summary xml:lang="nl">Een hulpmiddel om een live-USB-drive te maken met een editie van Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="pa">ਫੇਡੋਰਾ ਦੇ ਐਡੀਸ਼ਨ ਨਾਲ ਲਾਈਵ USB ਡਰਾਇਵ ਬਣਾਉਣ ਲਈ ਟੂਲ</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="pl">Narzędzie do tworzenia dysków USB typu Live z Fedorą</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="pt">Uma ferramenta para criar uma unidade USB "live" com uma edição do Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="pt-br">Uma ferramenta para criar uma unidade live USB com uma edição do Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="ru">Инструмент для создания Live USB-накопителя с Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="sk">Nástroj na vytváranie live USB diskov s niektorou edíciou Fedory</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="sl">Orodje za kreiranje živega pogona USB z izdajo Fedore</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="sq">Një mjet për krijim diskthi USB live me një version Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="sr">Алатка за стварање живих УСБ уређаја са издањима Fedora-е</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="sv">Ett verktyg för att skapa en live-USB-enhet med en utgåva av Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="ta">ஃபெடோரா பதிப்புடன் வரும் நேரடி இயக்கக USB வட்டை உருவாக்கும் ஒரு கருவி.</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="tr">Fedora sürümünü içeren canlı USB aygıtı yaratmanızı sağlayan araç</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="uk">Інструмент для створення портативних дисків USB із редакцією Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="zh-cn">一个用来创建 Live USB 启动盘的 Fedora 版工具</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="zh-tw">為各種 Fedora 版本製作 Live USB 裝置的工具</summary>
	<description>
		<p>A tool to create a bootable live USB drive with an edition of Fedora. Not only can Fedora Media Writer write an image to your flash drive, it can also download it for you. It offers official editions (Server, Workstation), Fedora spins (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...), and Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab,...). It provides basic information about each of them to help you make the right choice.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ar">أداة لإنشاء محرك أقراص USB مباشر قابل للإقلاع بإحدى إصدارات فيدورا. لا يقوم كاتب وسائط فيدورا بكتابة صورة القرص وحسب، بل بوسعه أيضًا تنزيلها لك. يدعم الإصدارات الرسمية (Server وWorkstation)، ومتحورات فيدورا (أسطح مكتب KDE وXfce وCinnamon...) ومختبرات فيدورا (Desgin Suite وSecurity Lab...). كما يعطيك معلومات أساسية عن كل واحد منهم لمساعدتك في اختيار الأنسب.</p>
		<p xml:lang="az">Fedora buraxılışı ilə yüklənə bilən Live USB disk yaratmaq üçün alət. Fedora Media Writer təkcə flash diskinizə görüntü yaza bilməz, həm də onu sizin üçün endirə bilər. O, rəsmi buraxılışları (Server, Workstation), Fedora spinləri (KDE Plazma Masaüstü, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...) və Fedora Labs (Dizayn Suite, Təhlükəsizlik Laboratoriyası,...) təklif edir. Düzgün seçim etməyinizə kömək etmək üçün onların hər biri haqqında əsas məlumatları təqdim edir.</p>
		<p xml:lang="be">Інструмент для стварэння загрузных Live USB-дыскаў з версіяй Fedora. Fedora Media Writer можа не толькі запісаць вобраз на флэш-накпляльнік, але і спампаваць яго. Прапануюцца афіцыйныя версіі (Server, Workstation), Fedora Spins (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop, ...) і Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab, ...). Прадастаўляецца асноўная інфармацыя па кожным з іх, якая дапамагае зрабіць правільны выбар.</p>
		<p xml:lang="bg">Инструмент за създаване на зареждащо живо USB устройство с Fedora. Fedora Media Writer записва образ на Вашия флаш диск, но също може и да го свали вместо Вас. Той предлага основните предназначения (Server, Workstation), Fedora компилации (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...) и Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab,...). Програмата предоставя основна информация за всяка от версиите, за да Ви помогне да направите правилния избор.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ca">Una eina per crear una unitat USB autònoma d'arrencada amb una edició de Fedora. Fedora Media Writer no només pot escriure una imatge en la vostra unitat flash, també pot baixar-la. Ofereix les edicions oficials (Server i Workstation), els spins de Fedora (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...), i els laboratoris de Fedora (Design Suite, Security Lab, ...). Proporciona la informació bàsica sobre cada un d'ells per ajudar a prendre la decisió correcta.</p>
		<p xml:lang="cs">Nástroj pro vytváření živých USB disků s některou z edicí Fedory. Nejen, že Fedora Media Writer zapíše obraz na váš disk, ale také ho pro vás stáhne. Nabízí oficiální vydání (Server, Workstation), Spiny Fedory (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...) a Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab,...). Obsahuje základní informace o každém z nich, aby pro vás bylo snažší udělat správnou volbu.</p>
		<p xml:lang="da">Et værktøj til at oprette et opstartsbart live-USB-drev med en udgave af Fedora. Fedora-medieskriver kan ikke blot skrive et aftryk til dit flash-drev, den kan også downloade det for dig. Den tilbyder officielle udgaver (Server, Workstation), Fedora-spins (KDE Plasma-skrivebord, Xfce-skrivebord, Cinnamon-skrivebord, ...) og Fedora Labs (designpakke, sikkerhedslaboratorie, ...). Den giver grundlæggende information om hver af dem for at hjælpe dig med at træffe det rigtige valg.</p>
		<p xml:lang="de">Ein Werkzeug, um einen bootfähigen Live-USB-Datenträger mit einer Ausgabe von Fedora zu erzeugen. Fedora Media Writer kann nicht nur ein Abbild auf einen Flash-Datenträger schreiben, sondern auch für Sie herunterladen. Es werden offizielle Ausgaben angeboten (Server, Workstation), Fedora Spins (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop …) und Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab …). Grundlegende Informationen zu jeder Ausgabe werden angezeigt, um Ihnen bei der Auswahl zu helfen.</p>
		<p xml:lang="es">Una herramienta para crear un USB vivo de arranque con una versión de Fedora. Fedora Media Writer no solamente escribe una imagen en su disco portátil, sino que además puede descargarla si no la tiene. Ofrece las versiones oficiales (Servidor, Estación de Trabajo), Ediciones especiales (Escritorio KDE Plasma, Escritorio Xfce, Escritorio Cinnamon...), y Fedora Labs (Herramientas de diseño, Laboratorio de Seguridad...). Proporciona información básica de cada una de ellas para ayudarle a elegir la más conveniente.</p>
		<p xml:lang="fa">یک ابزار برای ایجاد یک USB لایو با یک نسخهٔ فدورا. نه تنها Fedora Media Writer ایمیج را بر روی فلش مموری رایت کند، بلکه می تواند آن را برای شما دانلود نیز بکند. این نسخه های رسمی فدورا (سرور و استگاه کار)، چرخه های فدورا (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop و ...) و آزمایشگاه های فدورا ( مجموعهٔ طراحی، آزمایشگاه امنیت و ...) را شامل می شود. این اطلاعات پایه ای در مورد هر یک از این موارد ارائه می دهد تا به شما در انتخاب کمک کند.</p>
		<p xml:lang="fi">Työkalu, jolla voi luoda USB-muistista käynnistettävän asennusmedian Fedoralle. Luontityökalu osaa ladata levykuvan ja kirjoittaa sen USB-muistille. Tarjolla ovat viralliset versiot (Server ja Workstation), Fedoran Spinit (mm. KDE Plasma, Xfce, Cinnamon -työpöydät) sekä Fedora Lab -julkaisut (mm. Design Suite, Security Lab). Se antaa jokaisesta niistä perustiedot, auttaaksesi sinua valitsemaan.</p>
		<p xml:lang="fil">Isang tool para gumawa ng bootable na live USB drive na may edisyon ng Fedora. Hindi lamang maaaring magsulat ng imahe ang Fedora Media Writer sa iyong flash drive, maaari rin itong mag-download para sa iyo. Nag-aalok ito ng mga opisyal na edisyon (Server, Workstation), Fedora spins (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...), at Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab,...). Nagbibigay ito ng pangunahing impormasyon tungkol sa bawat isa sa kanila upang matulungan kang na pumili ng wasto.</p>
		<p xml:lang="fr">Un outil pour créer une disque USB live avec une version de Fedora. Non seulement Fedora Media Writer peut écrire une image sur votre disque USB, mais il peut aussi la télécharger pour vous. Il offre les éditions officielles (Server, Workstation), les Fedora Spins (environnements KDE Plasma, Xfce, Cinnamon…) et les Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab…). Il fournit des informations de base sur chacune de ces options pour vous permettre de faire le bon choix.</p>
		<p xml:lang="fur">Un strument par creâ une unitât USB Live inviabile cuntune edizion di Fedora. Scritor Supuarts di Fedora al pues no dome scrivi une imagjin su calvute, al pues ancje discjariâtile. Al ufrìs edizions uficiâi (Servidôr,Workstation), Fedora spins (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...) e Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab,...). Al furnìs informazions di base su ogniune di lôr par fâti sielzi ben.</p>
		<p xml:lang="he">כלי ליצירת כונן USB חי עם מהדורת Fedora. לא בלבד שכותב המדיה של Fedora מסוגל לכתוב תמונה אל כונן ההבזק, הוא יכול גם להורידה. מציע מהדורות רשמיות (Server, Workstation), הסבות Fedora (שולחן עבודה KDE Plasma, שולחן עבודה Xfce, שולחן עבודה Cinnamon,...), ומעבדות Fedora (ערכת עיצוב, מעבדת אבטחה). מספק מידע בסיסי על אודות כל אחד מהם לעזרה בבחירה הנכונה.</p>
		<p xml:lang="hr">Alat stvaranja pokretljivog USB uređaja za izdanja Fedore. Fedora zapisnik medija uz zapisivanje slika na vaš usb uređaj može i preuzimati slike umjesto vas. Nudi službena izdanja (Server, Workstation), Fedora spinove (KDE Plasma radnu površinu, Xfce radnu površinu, Cinnamon radnu površinu,...) i Fedora labos (Paket za dizajn, Sigurnosni labos,...). Omogućuje osnovne informacije o svakom izdanju kako bi vam olakšao odabir.</p>
		<p xml:lang="hu">Egy eszköz indítható live USB meghajtó készítéséhez a Fedora egy változatával. A Fedora médiaíró nem csak ki tudja írni a lemezképet, hanem le is tudja tölteni azt. A hivatalos, támogatott verziókat (Server, Workstation), a Fedora Spineket (KDE Plasma Desktop, XFCE Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...), és a Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab, …) lemezképeit nyújtja. Alapinformációkat is nyújt mindegyikről, hogy helyesen választhasson.</p>
		<p xml:lang="id">Alat untuk menciptakan drive USB live yang dapat di-boot dengan suatu edisi Fedora. Fedora Media Writer tidak hanya dapat menulis image ke flash disk Anda, itu juga dapat mengunduhkan untuk Anda. Menawarkan edisi resmi (Server, Workstation), Fedora spins (Desktop KDE Plasma, Desktop Xfce, Desktop Cinnamon, ...), dan Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab, ...). Menyediakan informasi dasar tentang masing-masing edisi untuk membantu Anda membuat pilihan yang benar.</p>
		<p xml:lang="it">Uno strumento per creare unità USB live con una edizione di Fedora. E non solo. Fedora Media Writer è in grado di scrivere immagini su unità flash USB, ma anche di effettuarne il download. Mette a disposizione le edizioni ufficiali (Server, Workstation), le spin di Fedora (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...), e le edizioni Fedora Lab (Design Suite, Security Lab,...). Fornisce inoltre informazioni di base su ciascuna di esse per aiutarti a fare la scelta giusta.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ja">このツールではFedoraのさまざまなエディションのLive USBメディアを作成することができます。Fedora Media Writerはイメージの書き込みだけではなくイメージのダウンロードも行なうことができます。オフィシャルイメージ(Server, Workstation)およびFedora Spin(KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktopなど)や、Fedora Labs(Design Suite, Security Labなど)に対応しています。確かな選択が行えるように、それぞれについての基本的な情報を提供します。</p>
		<p xml:lang="ka">ხელსაწყო Fedora-სთვის ცოცხალი USB დისკის შესაქმნელად. Fedora Media Writer-ს არა მხოლოდ ასლების ჩაწერა შეუძლია, არამედ მათი გადმოწერაც. ის გთავაზობთ ოფიციალურ გამოცემებს (სერვერი, სამუშაო მაგიდა), სპინები (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop და ა.შ.) და Fedora Labs-ი (დიზაინი, უსაფრთხოება და ა.შ.). ის გაჩვენებთ ძირითად ინფორმაციას ყველაფერზე, რასაც მონიშნავთ, რათა სწორი არჩევანის გაკეთებაში დაგეხმაროთ.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ko">페도라 배포판으로 부팅 가능한 라이브 USB 드라이브를 생성하는 도구입니다. 페도라 미디어 작성기는 사용자의 플래시 드라이브에 이미지를 쓸 수 있을 뿐만 아니라, 이를 내려 받을 수도 있습니다. 공식 배포판(서버, 웍스테이션), 페도라 스핀(KDE 플래즈마 데스크탑, Xfce 데스크탑, 시나몬 데스크탑,...), 그리고 페도라 Labs(디자인 제품군, 보안 랩,...) 등이 있습니다. 사용자에게 맞는 선택을 할 수 있도록 각 제품에 대한 기본 정보가 제공됩니다.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ml">ലൈവ് ആയ ഇമേജ് ഡിസ്കിനെ USB ഡ്രൈവ് ആകുന്ന ഉപകരണം. ഫെഡോറ മീഡിയ റൈറ്റർ ഉപയോഗിച്ച് കൊണ്ടു ഫെഡോറ ലൈവ് ഇമേജ് ഡൌൺലോഡ് ചെയ്യാനും സാദിക്കും. ഫെഡോറ വർക്സ്റ്റേഷൻ, ഫെഡോറ സെർവർ എന്നുള്ള ഔദ്യോഗിക ഇമേജുകൾ, ഫെഡോറ റെസ്പിൻ ഇമേജുകൾ (KDE Plasma ഡെസ്ക്ടോപ്പ്, Xfce ഡെസ്ക്ടോപ്പ്, Cinnamon ഡെസ്ക്ടോപ്പ്) , ഫെഡോറ ലാബ് ( ഡിസൈൻ Suite , സുരക്ഷാ ലാബ് ) എന്നിവ ഡൌൺലോഡ് ചെയ്യാനുള്ള ഓപ്ഷനും ലഭ്യമാണ്.</p>
		<p xml:lang="nl">Een hulpmiddel om een opstartbare live-USB-drive te maken met een oplage van Fedora. Fedora mediaschrijver kan niet alleen een image naar je flash drive schrijven, maar kan deze ook voor je downloaden. Het biedt officiële edities aan (Server, Workstation), Fedora spins (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...), en Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab,...). Het biedt basis informatie over elke editie aan om je de juiste keuze te laten maken.</p>
		<p xml:lang="pa">ਫੇਡੋਰਾ (Fedora) ਦੇ ਐਡੀਸ਼ਨਾਂ ਲਈ ਬੂਟ ਹੋਣ ਯੋਗ ਲਾਈਵ USB ਬਣਾਉਣ ਵਾਲਾ ਟੂਲ ਹੈ। Fedora ਮੀਡੀਆ ਰਾਇਟਰ ਨਾ ਸਿਰਫ਼ ਤੁਹਾਡੀ ਫਲੈਸ਼ ਡਰਾਇਵ ਉੱਤੇ ਈਮੇਜ਼ ਲਿਖ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ, ਪਰ ਇਹ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਲਈ ਡਾਊਨਲੋਡ ਵੀ ਕਰ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ। ਇਹ ਆਫਿਸ਼ਲ ਐਡੀਸ਼ਨ (ਸਰਵਰ, ਵਰਕਸਟੇਸ਼ਨ), ਫੇਡੋਰਾ ਸਪਿਨ (KDE ਪਲਾਜ਼ਮਾ ਡੈਸਕਟਾਪ, Xfce ਡੈਸਕਟਾਪ, ਸਿਨਾਮਨ ਡੈਸਕਟਾਪ,..) ਅਤੇ ਫੇਡੋਰਾ ਲੈਬਾਂ (ਡਿਜ਼ਾਇਨ ਸਵੀਟ, ਸਕਿਉਰਟੀ ਲੈਬ,..) ਪੇਸ਼ ਕਰਦਾ ਹੈ। ਇਹ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਚੋਣ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਉਹਨਾਂ ਵਿੱਚੋਂ ਹਰੇਕ ਬਾਰੇ ਸੰਖੇਪ ਜਿਹੀ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਦਿੰਦਾ ਹੈ।</p>
		<p xml:lang="pl">Narzędzie do tworzenia dysków USB typu Live z Fedorą. Fedora Media Writer może zapisywać obrazy na dyskach USB i je pobierać. Oferuje oficjalne edycje (Server, Workstation), dodatkowe obrazy (KDE Plasma, Xfce, Cinnamon…) i obrazy z Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab…). Dostarcza podstawowe informacje o obrazach, aby pomóc dokonać właściwego wyboru.</p>
		<p xml:lang="pt">Uma ferramenta para criar uma unidade USB de arranque "live" com uma edição do Fedora. O Fedora Media Writer não só pode gravar uma imagem na sua unidade USB, mas esta também pode transferi-las para si. Esta oferece edições oficiais (Servidor, Estação de trabalho), "spins" do Fedora (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...), e Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab,...). Esta fornece informação básica sobre cada uma delas para ajudá-lo a fazer a escolha certa.</p>
		<p xml:lang="pt-br">Uma ferramenta para criar dispositivos inicializáveis live USB com uma edição do Fedora. Não só o Fedora Media Writer pode gravar uma imagem em sua unidade flash, como também pode baixá-la para você. Ele oferece edições oficiais (Server, Workstation), Fedora spins (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop, ...) e Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab, ...). Ele fornece informações básicas sobre cada um deles para ajudá-lo a fazer a escolha certa.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ru">Инструмент для создания загрузочных Live USB-накопителей с версией Fedora. Fedora Media Writer может не только записать образ на флеш-накопитель, но и загрузить его. Предлагаются официальные версии (Server, Workstation), Fedora Spins (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...) и Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab,...). Предоставляется основная информация по каждому из них, помогающая сделать правильный выбор.</p>
		<p xml:lang="sk">Nástroj na vytváranie spúšťateľných live USB diskov s niektorou edíciou Fedory. Fedora Media Writer dokáže nielen zapísať obraz na váš USB kľúč, ale ho pre vás aj stiahnuť. Ponúka oficiálne edície (Server, Workstation), Fedora spiny (Pracovné prostredie KDE, Xfce, Cinnamon, ...) a Laboratóriá Fedora (Design Suite, Security Lab, ...). Poskytuje taktiež základné informácie o každej edícii, aby ste si mohli vybrať tú správnu.</p>
		<p xml:lang="sl">Orodje za ustvarjanje živega zagonskega pogona z izdajo Fedore. Ne samo, da lahko Fedora Media Writer napiše sliko na vaš pogon, ampak jo lahko tudi prenese za vas. Ponuja uradne izdaje (strežnik, delovna postaja), Fedora Spins (KDE Plasma Desktop, XFCE Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop, ...) in Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab, ...). Ponuja osnovne informacije o vsaki od njih, ki vam bodo pomagale pravilno izbirati.</p>
		<p xml:lang="sq">Një mjet për krijim diskthi USB live me një version Fedora. Fedora Media Writer jo vetëm që mund të shkruajë një pamje te diskthi juaj, mundet edhe ta shkarkojë atë për ju. Ju ofron versione zyrtare (Server, Workstation), degëzime Fedora(Desktop KDE Plasma, Desktop Xfce, Desktop Cinnamon,…), dhe Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab,...). Furnizon të dhëna bazë rreth secilit prej tyre për t’ju ndihmuar të bëni zgjedhjen e duhur.</p>
		<p xml:lang="sr">Алатка за стварање подизних, живих УСБ уређаја са издањима Fedora-е. Не само што Fedora Писач Медија може писати слике на ваш флеш уређај, он их такође може преузети уместо вас. Пружа званична издања (за сервере, радне станице), Fedora спинове (КДЕ Плазма окружење, Xfce окружење, Цинамон окружење,...) и Fedora Лабораторије (Design Suite, Security Lab,...). Такође пружа основне податке о сваком од издања и тиме вам помаже да направите добар избор.</p>
		<p xml:lang="sv">Ett verktyg för att skapa en startbar live-USB-enhet med en utgåva av Fedora. Inte endast kan Fedora Mediaskrivare kan inte bara skriva en avbild till din flash-enhet, den kan hämta den åt dig också. Den erbjuder officiella utgåvor (Server, Workstation), Fedoraspins (KDE Plasma-skrivbord, Xfce-skrivbord, Cinnamon-skrivbord, …), och Fedora Labb (Designsvit, Säkerhetslabb, …). Det erbjuder grundläggande information om var och en av dem för att hjälpa dig att göra rätt val.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ta">ஃபெடோரா பதிப்புடன் வரும் நேரடி இயக்கக USB வட்டை உருவாக்கும் ஒரு கருவி. ஃபெடோரா ஊடக இயக்கி உங்கள் USB வட்டை எழுதுவதற்கு மட்டுமல்ல, கூடுதலாக  பதிவிறக்கவும் செய்யலாம். இது Server, Workstation,  Fedora spins (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...), மற்றும் Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab,...) போன்ற பதிப்புகளையும் அளிக்கவல்லது. இது உங்களுக்கு உதவ  ஒவ்வொன்றின் அடி ப்படை தகவல்களையும்  அளிக்கும்.</p>
		<p xml:lang="tr">Bir Fedora sürümünü içeren canlı USB aygıtı yaratmanızı sağlayan bu araçla yalnızca görüntünün aygıtınıza yazılmasını değil aynı zamanda sizin için indirilmesini de sağlayabilirsiniz. Resmi sürümlerin (Sunucu, Masaüstü) yanı sıra Fedora seçkilerini (KDE Plasma Masaüstü, Xfce masaüstü, Cinnamon Masaüstü...) ve Fedora Lab'larını (Tasarım paketi, güvenlik paketi...) da indirebilir ve doğru seçimi yapmanızı sağlayacak temel bilgileri bulabilirsiniz.</p>
		<p xml:lang="uk">Інструмент для створення придатних до завантаження записів портативної системи Fedora на носіях USB. Fedora Media Writer може не лише записувати образи на вашу флешку, але отримувати ці образи з інтернету. Програма запропонує вам офіційні випуски (Server, Workstation), Fedora spins (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...) та випуски Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab,...). Вона надає основну інформацію щодо кожного з образів, що допоможе вам зробити правильний вибір.</p>
		<p xml:lang="zh-cn">一个为各种 Fedora 版本制作可启动 Live USB 设备的工具。Fedora Media Writer 不仅能将镜像写入优盘中，还能为你下载镜像。它提供官方版（Server、Workstation）、Fedora 定制版（KDE Plasma 桌面、Xfce 桌面、Cinnamon 桌面等）以及 Fedora 实验室（设计套件、安全实验室等）。它还提供各版本的基本信息来帮助你做选择。</p>
		<p xml:lang="zh-tw">為各種 Fedora 版本製作可開機 Live USB 裝置的工具。Fedora 媒體寫入器不只能將映像檔寫入您的快閃裝置中，它還能替您下載映像檔。它提供官方版（Server、Workstation）、Fedora Spins（KDE Plasma 桌面、Xfce 桌面、Cinnamon 桌面……等）、和 Fedora Labs（設計套組、安全實驗室……等）。它提供各版本的基本資訊來幫助您作選擇。</p>
		<p>Fedora Media Writer can also write other bootable ISOs loaded from your local disk, but keep in mind that it's only tested with Fedora images.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ar">بوسع كاتب وسائط فيدورا أيضًا كتابة صور الأقراص الأخرى القابلة للإقلاع من قرصك المحلي، مع العلم أنه لم يُختبر سوى على صور أقراص فيدورا.</p>
		<p xml:lang="az">Fedora Media Yazıcı yerli diskinizdən yüklənmiş digər yüklənə bilən İSO-ları da yaza bilər, lakin onun yalnız Fedora görüntü ilə sınaqdan keçirildiyini unutmayın.</p>
		<p xml:lang="be">Fedora Media Writer можа запісаць і іншыя загрузныя ISO-файлы, якія бяруцца з вашага лакальнага дыска, але майце на ўвазе, што ён правераны толькі з вобразамі Fedora.</p>
		<p xml:lang="bg">Fedora Media Writer също може да записва други зареждащи ISO образи, заредени от твърдия Ви диск, но имайте предвид, че това е тествано само с образи на Fedora.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ca">Fedora Media Writer també pot escriure altres ISO d'arrencada des del vostre disc local, però tingueu present que només s'ha provat amb les imatges de Fedora.</p>
		<p xml:lang="cs">Fedora Media Writer také dokáže zapsat jiné bootovatelné ISO obrazy z vašeho disku, ale mějte na paměti, že byl testovaný pouze s obrazy Fedory.</p>
		<p xml:lang="da">Fedora-medieskriver kan også skrive andre opstartsbare ISO'er indlæst fra din lokale disk, men husk på at den kun er testet med Fedora-aftryk.</p>
		<p xml:lang="de">Fedora Media Writer kann außerdem mit bootfähigen ISO-Abbildern von Ihrer Festplatte umgehen. Bitte bedenken Sie jedoch, dass das Programm nur mit Fedora-Abbildern getestet wurde.</p>
		<p xml:lang="es">Fedora Media Writer también puede escribir otras ISOs de arranque que tenga en su disco duro, pero tenga en cuenta que solo se prueba con imágenes de Fedora.</p>
		<p xml:lang="fa">همچنین Fedora Media Writer می تواند دیگر فایل های ISO قابل بوت موجود در دیسک محلی شما را رایت کند، اما در نظر داشته باشید که این فقط با فدورا آزمایش شده است.</p>
		<p xml:lang="fi">Fedora-median luontityökalulla voi kirjoittaa USB:lle myös muita ISO-tiedostoja, mutta työkalua on testattu vain Fedoran levykuvilla.</p>
		<p xml:lang="fil">Ang Fedora Media Writer ay maaari ding magsulat ng iba pang mga bootable na ISO na na-load mula sa iyong lokal na disk, ngunit tandaan na ito ay nasubok lamang sa mga larawan ng Fedora.</p>
		<p xml:lang="fr">Fedora Media Writer peut aussi écrire d’autres images ISO amorçables chargées depuis votre disque local, mais sachez bien qu’il n’a été testé qu’avec les images de Fedora.</p>
		<p xml:lang="fur">Scritôr Supuarts di Fedora al pues ancje scrivi altris ISO inviabilis, cjariadis sul disc fis locâl, ma ten iniments che al è stât provât dome cun lis imagjins di Fedora.</p>
		<p xml:lang="he">כותב המדיה של Fedora מסוגל גם לכתוב דמויות ISO ניתנות לאתחול אחרות מהכונן המקומי, אך מוטב לזכור שהוא נבדק רק עם דמויות של Fedora.</p>
		<p xml:lang="hr">Fedora zapisnik medija može zapisivati i druge pokretljive ISO slike učitane s vašeg čvrstog diska, ali zapamtite da je samo testiran s Fedora slikama.</p>
		<p xml:lang="hu">A Fedora médiaíró képes más indítható ISO-kat is kiírni a helyi lemezéről, de tartsa észben, hogy az alkalmazás csak Fedora lemezképekkel lett tesztelve.</p>
		<p xml:lang="id">Fedora Media Writer juga dapat menulis ISO yang dapat di-boot lain dari disk lokal Anda, tapi ingatlah bahwa ini hanya diuji untuk image Fedora.</p>
		<p xml:lang="it">Fedora Media Writer può inoltre creare altre ISO avviabili da immagini caricate dai dischi locali, ma va tenuto presente che è testato solo con le immagini Fedora.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ja">Fedora Media Writerはローカルディスクから読み込まれた他の起動可能なISOイメージを書き込むこともできますが、このツールはFedoraイメージでのみテストされていることに注意してください。</p>
		<p xml:lang="ka">Fedora Media Writer-ს თქვენი დისკიდან წაკითხული სხვა ჩატვირთვადი ISO ფაილების ჩაწერაც შეუძლია, მაგრამ, დაიმახსოვრეთ, რომ ის მხოლოდ Fedora-ის ასლებზეა დატესტილი.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ko">페도라 미디어 작성기는 또한 사용자의 로컬 디스크에서 적재된 다른 부팅 가능한 ISO에도 쓸 수 있지만, 페도라 이미지만 시험 되었으니 유의하기 바랍니다.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ml">ഫെഡോറ മാധ്യമ എഴുതുപകരണം ഉപയോഗിച്ച് ലോക്കൽ ഡിസ്കിലുള്ള ഐസോ എഴുതാനുള്ള സവിശേഷത ലഭ്യമാണ്, പക്ഷെ ഫെഡോറ ഡിസ്ക് ഇമേജ് മാത്രം പരിശോധന വിദേയം.</p>
		<p xml:lang="nl">Fedora mediaschrijver kan ook andere opstartbare ISO's schrijven die geladen zijn vanaf je lokale schijf, maar denk eraan dat dit alleen getest is voor Fedora images.</p>
		<p xml:lang="pa">ਫੇਡੋਰਾ ਮੀਡੀਆ ਰਾਇਟਰ ਤੁਹਾਡੀ ਲੋਕਲ ਡਿਸਕ ਤੋਂ ਲੋਡ ਕੀਤੇ ਹੋਰ ਬੂਟ ਹੋਣਯੋਗ ISO ਵੀ ਲਿਖ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ, ਪਰ ਧਿਆਨ ਰੱਖੋ ਕਿ ਇਹ ਕੇਵਲ ਫੇਡੋਰਾ ਈਮੇਜ਼ਾਂ ਲਈ ਹੀ ਜਾਂਚਿਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</p>
		<p xml:lang="pl">Fedora Media Writer może także zapisywać inne startowe pliki ISO z lokalnego dysku, ale należy pamiętać, że jest testowany tylko z obrazami Fedory.</p>
		<p xml:lang="pt">O Fedora Media Writer também consegue gravar outras ISOs carregadas a partir do seu disco local, mas tenha em atenção que este apenas foi testado com imagens do Fedora.</p>
		<p xml:lang="pt-br">O Fedora Media Writer também pode criar outras ISO inicializáveis a partir de seu disco local, mas tenha consciência de que isso só foi testado com as imagens do Fedora.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ru">Fedora Media Writer может записать и другие загрузочные ISO-файлы, которые берутся с вашего локального диска, но имейте в виду, что он проверен только с образами Fedora.</p>
		<p xml:lang="sk">Fedora Media Writer umožňuje tiež zapísať iné spustiteľné ISO obrazy z vášho disku. Nezabudnite však, že bol testovaný iba s obrazmi Fedory.</p>
		<p xml:lang="sl">Fedora Media Writer lahko piše tudi druge naložene slike OS iz vašega lokalnega diska, a zavedajte se, da je bilo to preverjeno samo s slikami OS Fedora.</p>
		<p xml:lang="sq">Fedora Media Writer mund të shkruajë edhe ISO të tjera të nisshme të ngarkuara mga disku juaj vendor, por mos harroni se është provuar vetëm me pamje Fedora.</p>
		<p xml:lang="sr">Fedora Писач Медија такође може писати друге подизне ISO-е учитане са вашег локалног диска али знајте да се испробава само са Fedora сликама система.</p>
		<p xml:lang="sv">Fedora Mediaskrivare kan även skriva andra startbara ISO:er som hämtas från din lokala disk, men kom ihåg att den bara har testats med Fedoraavbilder.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ta">ஃபெடோரா ஊடக இயக்கி மற்ற ISOக்களையும் இயக்கவல்லது. ஆனால் இது ஃபெடோரா வகை ISO-க்களை வைத்து மட்டுமே சோதிக்கப்பட்டது என்பதனை நினைவில் கொள்ளவும்.</p>
		<p xml:lang="tr">Fedora Ortam Yazıcı aygıtınızda yer alan önyüklenebilen diğer ISO görüntülerinin yazılmasında da kullanılabilir ama aracın yalnızca Fedora görüntüleri ile denendiğini lütfen aklınızda bulundurun.</p>
		<p xml:lang="uk">Fedora Media Writer можна також скористатися для запису інших придатних до завантаження образів ISO з локального диска, але слід мати на увазі, що тестування програми виконувалося лише для образів Fedora.</p>
		<p xml:lang="zh-cn">Fedora Media Writer 也可以从你本地磁盘载入可启动的 ISO 文件，但请注意这个工具只测试过 Fedora 镜像。</p>
		<p xml:lang="zh-tw">Fedora 媒體寫入器也能寫入您本地端磁碟上的其他可開機 ISO 檔，但請謹記只有 Fedora 映像檔有經過測試。</p>
	</description>
	<keywords>
        <keyword>iso</keyword>
        <keyword>fedora</keyword>
        <keyword>usb</keyword>
        <keyword>writer</keyword>
        <keyword>live</keyword>
        <keyword>spin</keyword>
        <keyword>creator</keyword>
        <keyword>media</keyword>
    </keywords>
	<url type="homepage">https://github.com/FedoraQt/MediaWriter</url>
	<screenshots>
	    <screenshot type="default"><image type="source">https://github.com/FedoraQt/MediaWriter/raw/main/dist/screenshots/linux_main.png</image></screenshot>
	    <screenshot><image type="source">https://github.com/FedoraQt/MediaWriter/raw/main/dist/screenshots/linux_select_release.png</image></screenshot>
	</screenshots>
	<developer_name>Jan Grulich</developer_name>
	<update_contact>jgrulich@redhat.com</update_contact>
	<content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
	<releases>
		<release version="5.0.1" date="2022-05-13"/>
	</releases>
</component>
