<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2016 Jiri Eischmann <eischmann@redhat.com> -->
<application>
	<id type="desktop">mediawriter.desktop</id>
	<project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
	<metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
	<name>Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="cs">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="uk">Fedora Media Writer</name>
	<summary>A tool to create a live USB drive with an edition of Fedora</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="cs">Nástroj pro vytváření živých USB disků s některou z edicí Fedory</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="uk">Інструмент для створення портативних дисків USB із редакцією Fedora</summary>
	<description>
		<p>A tool to create a bootable live USB drive with an edition of Fedora. Not only can Fedora Media Writer write an image to your flash drive, it can also download it for you. It offers official editions (Server, Workstation), Fedora spins (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...), and Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab,...). It provides basic information about each of them to help you make the right choice.</p>
		<p xml:lang="cs">Nástroj pro vytváření živých USB disků s některou z edicí Fedory. Nejen, že Fedora Media Writer zapíše obraz na váš disk, ale také ho pro vás stáhne. Nabízí oficiální vydání (Server, Workstation), Spiny Fedory (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...) a Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab,...). Obsahuje základní informace o každém z nich, aby pro vás bylo snažší udělat správnou volbu.</p>
		<p xml:lang="uk">Інструмент для створення придатних до завантаження записів портативної системи Fedora на носіях USB. Fedora Media Writer може не лише записувати образи на вашу флешку, але отримувати ці образи з інтернету. Програма запропонує вам офіційні випуски (Server, Workstation), Fedora spins (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...) та випуски Fedora Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab,...). Вона надає основну інформацію щодо кожного з образів, що допоможе вам зробити правильний вибір.</p>
		<p>Fedora Media Writer can also write other bootable ISOs loaded from your local disk, but keep in mind that it's only tested with Fedora images.</p>
		<p xml:lang="cs">Fedora Media Writer také dokáže zapsat jiné bootovatelné ISO obrazy z vašeho disku, ale mějte na paměti, že byl testovaný pouze s obrazy Fedory.</p>
		<p xml:lang="uk">Fedora Media Writer можна також скористатися для запису інших придатних до завантаження образів ISO з локального диска, але слід мати на увазі, що тестування програми виконувалося лише для образів Fedora.</p>
	</description>
	<keywords>
        <keyword>iso</keyword>
        <keyword>fedora</keyword>
        <keyword>usb</keyword>
        <keyword>writer</keyword>
        <keyword>live</keyword>
        <keyword>spin</keyword>
        <keyword>creator</keyword>
        <keyword>media</keyword>
    </keywords>
	<url type="homepage">https://github.com/MartinBriza/MediaWriter</url>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot type="default">https://github.com/MartinBriza/MediaWriter/raw/master/dist/screenshots/expanded.png</screenshot>
		<screenshot>https://github.com/MartinBriza/MediaWriter/raw/master/dist/screenshots/details.png</screenshot>
	</screenshots>
	<update_contact>mbriza@redhat.com</update_contact>
</application>
